堅定留下的忠心
Steadfast devotion to stay
沒有離去的念頭
Without temptation to stray
永遠是如此迅速
Always in motion so high
目的地只有一個
One destination to find
從空中俯瞰
Eyeing from the air
與五花八門的鳥一起
with one of every avian
底下的大地
down below at earth
和大地之上
and those upon
無數選擇中
Out of such a choice,
無數噪音中
out of all the noise
只有少數會
Only few will be
被他記得
in mind of one
只有少數會
Few can belong
堅定留下的忠心
Steadfast devotion to stay
沒有離去的念頭
Without temptation to stray
永遠是如此迅速
Always in motion so high
目的地只有一個
One destination to find
是我的榮幸
Pleasure's mine to be
能服務我的朋友
in service of a friend to me
我唯一的夢想
'Tis my only dream
以及使命
and destiny
常常我覺得
Often times I feel
如此不中用
so inadequate
除了家人外
Who am I to you
我還是什麼？
but family?
噢，幫我看清
Oh help me see
幫我看清
Help me see
噢，幫我看清
Oh, help me see
幫我看清
Help me see
堅定留下的忠心
Steadfast devotion to stay
沒有離去的念頭
Without temptation to stray
永遠是如此迅速
Always in motion so high
目的地只有一個
One destination to find